{"1": {"question": "Which of the following did Chopin not write? ", "correct": "Nocturnes in D major", "incorrect": ["Nocturnes in B flat minor", "Nocturnes in E flat major", "Nocturnes in A minor"]}, "2": {"question": "Which of the following did Schumann not write? ", "correct": "Piano Concerto in A major", "incorrect": ["Album for the Young", "Papillons", "Scenes from childhood"]}, "3": {"question": "Which of the following did Debussy not write? ", "correct": "Papillons", "incorrect": ["La mer", "Arabesques", "Clair de lune"]}, "4": {"question": "What period of composition does Chopin represent? ", "correct": "Romantic", "incorrect": ["Classical", "Baroque", "Renaissance"]}, "5": {"question": "What period of composition does Schumann represent? ", "correct": "Romantic", "incorrect": ["Classical", "Baroque", "Renaissance"]}, "6": {"question": "What period of composition does Debussy represent?", "correct": "Romantic", "incorrect": ["Classical", "Baroque", "Renaissance"]}, "7": {"question": "Which of the following is not a characteristic of Chopin's style of composition?", "correct": "Not very technically demanding", "incorrect": ["More dependency on the pedal", "Elaboration over a bass note", "Nationalistic elements"]}, "8": {"question": "Which of the following is not a characteristic of Schumann's style of composition?", "correct": "Chromaticism", "incorrect": ["Precise, rhythmical patterns", "Fantastical"]}, "9": {"question": "Which of the following is not a characteristic of Debussy's style of composition?", "correct": "Simple, somewhat basic rhythms", "incorrect": ["Non-traditional scales", "Fragmentary melodies", "Use of pedal for colour"]}, "10": {"question": "Which of the following composers did not often write chamber works for strings and piano? ", "correct": "Czerny", "incorrect": ["Debussy", "Haydn", "Brahms"]}, "11": {"question": "Which of the following four woodwind instruments is not usually found in an orchestra?", "correct": "Piccolo ", "incorrect": ["Bassoon", "Clarinet", "Flute"]}, "12": {"question": "What is the lowest note played by the bassoon?", "correct": "Bb1", "incorrect": ["Bb2", "A1", "A2"]}, "13": {"question": "What is the lowest note played by the clarinet?", "correct": "E3", "incorrect": ["D3", "E4", "D4"]}, "14": {"question": "What is the lowest note played by the oboe? ", "correct": "Bb4", "incorrect": ["Ab4", "A4", "B4"]}, "15": {"question": "What is the lowest note played by the flute? ", "correct": "C4", "incorrect": ["D4", "Eb4", "G4"]}, "16": {"question": "What is the highest note played by the bassoon?", "correct": "G5", "incorrect": ["Ab5", "B5", "E5"]}, "17": {"question": "What is the highest note played by the clarinet? ", "correct": "C7", "incorrect": ["B7", "D7", "Bb7"]}, "18": {"question": "What is the highest note played by the oboe? ", "correct": "G6", "incorrect": ["A6", "Ab6", "Bb6"]}, "19": {"question": "What is the highest note played by the flute? ", "correct": "C7", "incorrect": ["Bb7", "B7", "E7"]}, "20": {"question": "Which of the following 4 instruments does not use the treble clef? ", "correct": "Bassoon", "incorrect": ["Oboe", "Clarinet", "Flute"]}, "21": {"question": "Which two clefs are used by the bassoon? ", "correct": "Bass clef and tenor clef", "incorrect": ["Tenor clef and alto clef", "Bass clef and alto clef", "Tenor clef and treble clef"]}, "22": {"question": "What tuning of clarinet apart from Bb is most commonly found in orchestras? ", "correct": "Clarinet in A", "incorrect": ["Clarinet in Eb", "Clarinet in C", "Clarinet in G"]}, "23": {"question": "What key is the flute most commonly tuned to? ", "correct": "C", "incorrect": ["Bb", "A", "Eb"]}, "24": {"question": "What key is the oboe most commonly tuned to? ", "correct": "C", "incorrect": ["Bb", "A", "Eb"]}, "25": {"question": "What key is the clarinet most commonly tuned to? ", "correct": "Bb", "incorrect": ["C", "A", "Eb"]}, "26": {"question": "What key is the bassoon most commonly tuned to? ", "correct": "C", "incorrect": ["Bb", "A", "Eb"]}}